Guide to the Records of the Communications Workers of America, Local 1150 WAG.059
Tamiment Library and Robert F. Wagner Labor Archives
- Series II: Minutes, 1940-1984; 546905
  - Grievance Committee, 1955-1956; 546927 (Box 2, Folder 23)
  - Grievance Committee, 1957-1958; 546926 (Box 2, Folder 24)
  - Grievance Committee, 1959-1960; 546925 (Box 2, Folder 25)
  - Grievance Committee, 1961; 546924 (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Grievance Committee, 1962-1964; 546923 (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - Grievance Committee, 1965-1967; 546922 (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - Grievance Committee, [1968-1978]; 546921 (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - Grievance Committee, 1979-1982; 546920 (Box 3, Folder 4a)
  - Grievance Committee: meetings with AT&T Interdepartmental Cttee (re: Blood Drives), 1949, 1951; 546919 (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - Committee on the Future, 1981-1982; 546918 (Box 3, Folder 5a)
  - Committee on Hours and Schedules, 1951-1955, 1961-1962; 546917 (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - Concerned Women Committee (CWC), 1979, 1981; 546916 (Box 3, Folder 6a)
  - Transit Strike Meetings, 1980; 546915 (Box 3, Folder 6b)
  - Membership Committee, 1952, undated; 546914 (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - Overtime Equalization Committee, Plant Section (with correspondence to 1963), 1952, 1956-1957; 546913 (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - Seniority of Hours Committee, Traffic Section, 1940-1956; 546912 (Box 3, Folder 9)
  - Social Committee, 1947-1948; 546911 (Box 3, Folder 10)
  - Strike Committee, 1947; 546910 (Box 3, Folder 11)
  - Vacation Committee, 1961-1962; 546909 (Box 3, Folder 11a)
  - Welfare Committee, [1951-1953]; 546908 (Box 3, Folder 12)
  - NYC Area Council and Downstate, 1955-1965; 546907 (Box 3, Folder 13)
  - Essex-West Hudson Labor Council AFL-CIO (NJ), 1965; 546906 (Box 3, Folder 14)
- Series III: Correspondence, 1939-1986; 546774
  - FLLTW National Office, NYC, 1943; 546904 (Box 3, Folder 15)
  - FLLTW and NFTW National Office, 1944-1946; 546903 (Box 3, Folder 16)
  - FLLTW National Office, NYC with local officers (Branches 101 & 127), Dec 1942-May 1946; 546902 (Box 3, Folder 17)
  - FLLTW: Office management corresp., 1942-1943; 546901 (Box 3, Folder 18)
  - FLLTW Branch 127 with other Branches, 1939-1942; 546900 (Box 3, Folder 19)
  - FLLTW Branch 127 with Branch representatives, 1940-1942; 546899 (Box 3, Folder 20)
  - FLLTW Branch 127 with members, 1940-1942; 546898 (Box 3, Folder 21)
  - FLLTW Branch 127 re: "Maternity Temporary" employees, 1939-1940; 546897 (Box 3, Folder 22)
  - FLLTW Branch 127, general, 1941-1942; 546896 (Box 3, Folder 23)
  - FLLTW Traffic Branch 101, general, 1943-1946; 546895 (Box 3, Folder 24)
  - FLLTW Branch 7001 & AUTW Local 1: Chairman's corresp., 1942-1946; 546894 (Box 3, Folder 25)
  - ATTIS, 1984; 546893 (Box 3, Folder 25a)
  - AUTW National Office, NYC (incl. reports), 1946, 1948-1949; 546892 (Box 3, Folder 26)
  - AUTW Local 1, 1946-1950; 546891 (Box 3, Folder 27)
  - CWA (International), Washington, DC, Jun 1949-1951; 546890 (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - CWA (International), Washington, DC, 1952-Mar-55; 546889 (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - CWA (International), Washington, DC, Jul 1955-Apr 1956; 546888 (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - CWA (International), Washington, DC, 1956-1958; 546887 (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - CWA (International), Washington, DC, 1959; 546886 (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - CWA (International), Washington, DC, 1960-1961; 546885 (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - CWA (International), Washington, DC, 1962-1963; 546884 (Box 4, Folder 7)
  - CWA (International), Washington, DC, 1964-1965; 546883 (Box 4, Folder 8)
  - CWA (International), Washington, DC, 1966-Jul 1967; 546882 (Box 4, Folder 9)
  - CWA (International), Washington, DC, Aug 1967-1968; 546881 (Box 4, Folder 10)
  - CWA (International), Washington, DC, 1969; 546880 (Box 4, Folder 11)
  - CWA (International), Washington, DC, 1970; 546879 (Box 4, Folder 12)
  - CWA (International), Washington, DC, 1971; 546878 (Box 4, Folder 13)
  - CWA (International), Washington, DC, 1972; 546877 (Box 4, Folder 14)
  - CWA (International), Washington, DC, 1973; 546876 (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - CWA (International), Washington, DC, 1974-Jul 1975; 546875 (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - CWA (International), Washington, DC, Aug 1975-1979; 546874 (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - CWA (International), Washington, DC, 1981-1986; 546873 (Box 5, Folder 4)
  - CWA (International), Washington, DC (Legislative/PAC material), 1950-1975, undated; 546872 (Box 5, Folder 5)
  - CWA, Secretary-Treasurer, 1952-1956, 1959-1965; 546871 (Box 5, Folder 6)
  - CWA, Secretary-Treasurer, 1966-1969; 546870 (Box 5, Folder 7)
  - CWA, Secretary-Treasurer, 1970-1976; 546869 (Box 5, Folder 8)
  - CWA, Secretary-Treasurer, 1970-1986; 546868 (Box 5, Folder 9)
  - CWA, Long Lines National Office, 1950-1951; 546867 (Box 5, Folder 10)
  - CWA, Long Lines National Office, 1952-1955; 546866 (Box 5, Folder 11)
  - CWA, Long Lines National Office, Jun 1955-1956; 546865 (Box 5, Folder 12)
  - CWA, Long Lines National Office, 1957-1958; 546864 (Box 5, Folder 13)
  - CWA, Long Lines National Office, 1959-1961; 546863 (Box 5, Folder 14)
  - CWA, Long Lines National Office: Bargaining Unit, 1962-1965; 546862 (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - CWA, Long Lines National Office: Bargaining Unit, 1966-1967; 546861 (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - CWA, Long Lines National Office: Bargaining Unit, 1968-1975, 1978, 1984; 546860 (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - CWA, Long Lines National Office: Bargaining Unit, 1971-1980; 546859 (Box 6, Folder 4)
  - CWA, Long Lines National Office: National Director, 1975-1982; 546858 (Box 6, Folder 5)
  - CWA, Long Lines National Office: National Director, 1983-1984; 546857 (Box 6, Folder 6)
  - CWA District 1, May 1951-1955; 546856 (Box 6, Folder 7)
  - CWA District 1, 1956-1957; 546855 (Box 6, Folder 8)
  - CWA District 1, 1958; 546854 (Box 6, Folder 9)
  - CWA District 1, 1959-1960; 546853 (Box 6, Folder 10)
  - CWA District 1, 1961-1962; 546852 (Box 6, Folder 11)
  - CWA District 1, 1963-1964; 546851 (Box 6, Folder 12)
  - CWA District 1, 1966-1968; 546850 (Box 6, Folder 13)
  - CWA District 1, 1969-1970; 546849 (Box 6, Folder 14)
  - CWA District 1, 1971-1972; 546848 (Box 6, Folder 15)
  - CWA District 1, 1973-1974, 1978; 546847 (Box 6, Folder 16)
  - Local Officers: President/Vice-President, 1946-1953; 546846 (Box 6, Folder 17)
  - Local Officers: President/Vice-President, 1954-1959; 546845 (Box 6, Folder 18)
  - Local Officers: President/Vice-President, 1960-1975; 546844 (Box 7, Folder 1)
  - Local Officers: President/Vice-President, 1977-1978; 546843 (Box 7, Folder 2)
  - Local Officers: President/Vice-President, 1979; 546842 (Box 7, Folder 3)
  - Local Officers: President/Vice-President, 1980; 546841 (Box 7, Folder 4)
  - Local Officers: President/Vice-President, 1981-1982; 546840 (Box 7, Folder 5)
  - Local Officers: President/Vice-President, 1983; 546839 (Box 7, Folder 6)
  - Local Officers: President/Vice-President, 1984; 546838 (Box 7, Folder 7)
  - Local Officers: President/Vice-President, 1985; 546837 (Box 7, Folder 8)
  - Local Officers: President/Vice-President, 1986-1987; 546836 (Box 7, Folder 9)
  - Local Officers with Management, 1951-1952; 546835 (Box 7, Folder 10)
  - Local Officers with Management, 1953-1955; 546834 (Box 7, Folder 11)
  - Local Officers with Management, 1956-1961; 546833 (Box 7, Folder 12)
  - Local Officers with Management, 1962-1967; 546832 (Box 7, Folder 13)
  - Local Officers with Management, 1968-1979; 546831 (Box 7, Folder 14)
  - Local Officers with Management, 1984-1985; 546830 (Box 7, Folder 15)
  - Local Secretary-Treasurer, 1953-1966; 546829 (Box 7, Folder 16)
  - Local Secretary-Treasurer, 1967-1970; 546828 (Box 7, Folder 17)
  - Local Secretary-Treasurer, 1978-1986; 546827 (Box 8, Folder 1)
  - Executive Board, 1979-1985; 546826 (Box 8, Folder 2)
  - Insurance Committee, 1957; 546825 (Box 8, Folder 3)
  - Local Committee Members, 1946-1959; 546824 (Box 8, Folder 4)
  - Legislative Committee, [1946-1972]; 546823 (Box 8, Folder 5)
  - Organizing & Education Committees, 1946-1959; 546822 (Box 8, Folder 6)
  - Organizing & Education Committees, 1961-1967, 1971-1975, undated; 546821 (Box 8, Folder 7)
  - Scholarship Committee, 1962-1963, 1965; 546820 (Box 8, Folder 8)
  - Social Committee, 1946-1966; 546819 (Box 8, Folder 9)
  - Welfare Committee, 1953, 1957-1968; 546818 (Box 8, Folder 10)
  - Administrative Section Chair, 1955, 1960-1970, 1978-1980; 546817 (Box 8, Folder 11)
  - Plant Section Chair, 1950-1951; 546816 (Box 8, Folder 12)
  - Plant Section Chair, 1952-1953, 1960-1975, 1979-1980; 546815 (Box 8, Folder 13)
  - Traffic Section Chair, 1950, [1953-1974], 1979-1980; 546814 (Box 8, Folder 14)
  - Stewards, 1945-1949; 546813 (Box 8, Folder 15)
  - Stewards, 1950-1953; 546812 (Box 8, Folder 16)
  - Stewards, 1955-1964; 546811 (Box 9, Folder 1)
  - Stewards, 1965-1967; 546810 (Box 9, Folder 2)
  - Stewards, 1968-1969; 546809 (Box 9, Folder 3)
  - Stewards, 1970-1973; 546808 (Box 9, Folder 4)
  - Stewards, 1974-1976; 546807 (Box 9, Folder 5)
  - Stewards, 1977-1978; 546806 (Box 9, Folder 6)
  - Stewards, 1981-1983; 546805 (Box 9, Folder 7)
  - Members, 1951-1956; 546804 (Box 9, Folder 8)
  - Members, 1957-1959; 546803 (Box 9, Folder 9)
  - Members, 1960-1966; 546802 (Box 9, Folder 10)
  - Members, 1967-1969; 546801 (Box 9, Folder 11)
  - Members, 1970-1976; 546800 (Box 9, Folder 12)
  - Members, 1978-1986; 546799 (Box 9, Folder 13)
  - Members' resignations, 1948-1956; 546798 (Box 10, Folder 1)
  - Members' resignations, 1957-1974, 1983; 546797 (Box 10, Folder 2)
  - Life Membership File, 1959, 1961-1965; 546796 (Box 10, Folder 3)
  - Life Membership File, 1966-1967; 546795 (Box 10, Folder 4)
  - Life Membership File, 1968-1969; 546794 (Box 10, Folder 5)
  - AUTW & CWA locals, 1946-1950; 546793 (Box 10, Folder 6)
  - CWA locals, 1951-1962; 546792 (Box 10, Folder 7)
  - CWA locals, 1965-1974; 546791 (Box 10, Folder 8)
  - Office Employees International Union (Locals 344 & 153), 1959-1965; 546790 (Box 10, Folder 9)
  - Other unions, 1946- 1951; 546789 (Box 10, Folder 10)
  - Other unions, 1955-1959, 1961-1965, 1971; 546788 (Box 10, Folder 11)
  - NYC Central Labor Council, 1960-1969; 546787 (Box 10, Folder 12)
  - NYC Central Labor Council, 1970-1975; 546786 (Box 10, Folder 13)
  - NY State CIO Council, 1955, 1957, 1984; 546785 (Box 10, Folder 14)
  - NJ State CIO Council, 1957-1958, 1960-1961; 546784 (Box 10, Folder 15)
  - NY State Dept. of Labor, 1959; 546783 (Box 10, Folder 16)
  - US Dept. of Labor, 1958, 1961; 546782 (Box 10, Folder 17)
  - Attorneys, 1955-1984; 546781 (Box 10, Folder 18)
  - General correspondence, 1948-1951; 546780 (Box 10, Folder 19)
  - General correspondence, 1951-1952; 546779 (Box 10, Folder 20)
  - General correspondence, 1955-1964; 546778 (Box 10, Folder 21)
  - General correspondence, 1965-1966; 546777 (Box 11, Folder 1)
  - General correspondence, 1967-1969; 546776 (Box 11, Folder 2)
  - General correspondence, 1970-1975; 546775 (Box 11, Folder 3)
- Series IV: Election and Referendum Records, 1946-1990; 546730
  - Elections Committee, Manual (notes & drafts), undated; 546773 (Box 11, Folder 4)
  - Balloting Committee: reports, etc., 1946-1955; 546772 (Box 11, Folder 5)
  - Balloting Summaries, local and national, 1946-1953; 546771 (Box 11, Folder 6)
  - AUTW Local 1 & CWA Local 1150: election results, 1946-1954; 546770 (Box 11, Folder 7)
  - Elections Committee: correspondence, 1946-1952; 546769 (Box 11, Folder 8)
  - Elections Committee: correspondence: ballots, resolutions, and membership lists, 1946-1951; 546768 (Box 11, Folder 9)
  - AUTW Local 1, Elections, 1947-1949; 546767 (Box 11, Folder 10)
  - Balloting Committee: corresp. and report, 1950; 546766 (Box 11, Folder 11)
  - AUTW Local 1, Letters of notification, 1950; 546765 (Box 11, Folder 12)
  - Elections Committee: corresp., reports, ballots, 1951-1953; 546764 (Box 11, Folder 13)
  - Elections Committee: corresp., reports, ballots, 1954-1955, 1964; 546763 (Box 11, Folder 14)
  - Elections, 1954; 546762 (Box 11, Folder 15)
  - General Election: notices, 1954; 546761 (Box 11, Folder 16)
  - General Election: notices and Convention: notices, reports, and corresp., 1956; 546760 (Box 11, Folder 17)
  - Elections Committee, 1956-1965; 546759 (Box 11, Folder 18)
  - General Election: corresp., report, 1957; 546758 (Box 11, Folder 19)
  - Convention delegates, 1957-1959; 546757 (Box 11, Folder 20)
  - General Elections: results, 1957-1959; 546756 (Box 11, Folder 21)
  - Referendum, strike vote, contract ratification, 1958; 546755 (Box 11, Folder 22)
  - General Elections: corresp., 1958-1959; 546754 (Box 11, Folder 23)
  - Referenda, Special Election, 1959; 546753 (Box 11, Folder 24)
  - Referenda, elections, 1960-1961; 546752 (Box 11, Folder 25)
  - Elections, contract ratification, 1961; 546751 (Box 11, Folder 26)
  - Elections, contract ratification, 1962-1963, 1965; 546750 (Box 11, Folder 27)
  - Elections, 1963; 546749 (Box 11, Folder 28)
  - Special Election, 1963, 1964; 546748 (Box 11, Folder 29)
  - Elections, Contract Ratification, 1964, 1965; 546747 (Box 11, Folder 30)
  - Dues Increase Referendum, 1960, 1965-1966, 1971-1975; 546746 (Box 12, Folder 1)
  - Elections, 1966-1967; 546745 (Box 12, Folder 2)
  - Elections, 1968-1969; 546744 (Box 12, Folder 3)
  - Elections, 1970; 546743 (Box 12, Folder 4)
  - Special Election, 1970; 546742 (Box 12, Folder 5)
  - Elections Committee, 1962-1991; 546741 (Box 12, Folder 6)
  - General Election, 1972-1973; 546740 (Box 12, Folder 7)
  - Elections, referenda, 1975-1976; 546739 (Box 12, Folder 8)
  - Special Election, 1975, 1978; 546738 (Box 12, Folder 9)
  - Elections, referenda, 1977-1980; 546737 (Box 12, Folder 10)
  - Elections, 1981-1984; 546736 (Box 12, Folder 11)
  - Elections (challenged), 1984-1985; 546735 (Box 12, Folder 12)
  - Elections, 1987-1990; 546734 (Box 12, Folder 13)
  - Stewards: reports on additions and changes, 1967-1976, 1978; 546733 (Box 12, Folder 14)
  - Campaign materials, 1957-1979; 546732 (Box 12, Folder 15)
  - Campaign materials, 1980, 1984, 1987-1988; 546731 (Box 12, Folder 16)
- Series V: Financial Records [See also Local and International Secretary-Treasurers' Correspondence in Series III], 1939-1988; 546710
  - Notes on dues rates, 1939-1971; 546729 (Box 12, Folder 17)
  - FLLTW and AUTW, Treasurer's Reports, 1940-1958; 546728 (Box 12, Folder 18)
  - AUTW Local 1: reports, etc., 1946-1950; 546727 (Box 12, Folder 19)
  - AUTW Local 1: receipts for expenses, 1948; 546726 (Box 12, Folder 20)
  - AUTW Local 1: dues in arrears, Jan 1949-Apr 1949; 546725 (Box 13, Folder 1)
  - AUTW Local 1: dues in arrears, May 1949-Apr 1950; 546724 (Box 13, Folder 2)
  - AUTW Local 1: dues in arrears: dues payments, Jan 1951-Mar 1951; 546723 (Box 13, Folder 3)
  - CWA Local 1150: chart of accounts, undated; 546722 (Box 13, Folder 4)
  - CWA Local 1150: chart of accounts: dues payments, Apr 1951-Jun 1951; 546721 (Box 13, Folder 5)
  - CWA Local 1150: chart of accounts: committee reports & proposals, 1951-1959; 546720 (Box 13, Folder 6)
  - CWA Local 1150: chart of accounts: reports of annual audit, 1952-1970; 546719 (Box 13, Folder 7)
  - CWA Local 1150: chart of accounts: monthly reports, 1949-1955; 546718 (Box 13, Folder 8)
  - CWA Local 1150: chart of accounts: defense fund, 1955-1956; 546717 (Box 13, Folder 9)
  - CWA Local 1150: chart of accounts: monthly reports, 1960-1964, 1977-1978; 546716 (Box 13, Folder 10)
  - CWA Local 1150: chart of accounts: monthly reports, 1979, 1983-1986; 546715 (Box 13, Folder 11)
  - CWA Local 1150: chart of accounts: recruiting incentives, 1967-1970; 546714 (Box 13, Folder 12)
  - CWA Local 1150: chart of accounts: report forms and regulations, 1961-1965; 546713 (Box 13, Folder 13)
  - CWA (International): auditor's annual reports, 1952-1967; 546712 (Box 13, Folder 14)
  - CWA (International): Finance Committee documents & Ways and Means Committee report, 1969-1971; 546711 (Box 13, Folder 15)
- Series VI: Bargaining and Arbitration Records, 1944-1986; 546640
  - Agreement: AT&T, Long Lines Dept. and FLLTW, 1945; 546709 (Box 13, Folder 16)
  - Articles of Agreement: General Routine and Plant Routines; Contract Provisions, 1944-1947; 546708 (Box 13, Folder 17)
  - Contracts; Agreements, 1944-1946, 1957, 1968; 546707 (Box 13, Folder 18)
  - Contracts; Agreements, 1948-1953; 546706 (Box 13, Folder 19)
  - Contracts; Agreements, 1948-1953; 546705 (Box 13, Folder 20)
  - Contracts; Agreements, 1948-1952; 546704 (Box 13, Folder 21)
  - Memos of Agreement, 1952; 546703 (Box 13, Folder 22)
  - Memos of Agreement, 1953; 546702 (Box 13, Folder 23)
  - Bargaining demands, 1954; 546701 (Box 14, Folder 1)
  - Bargaining demands, 1955; 546700 (Box 14, Folder 2)
  - Bargaining reports, 1955; 546699 (Box 14, Folder 3)
  - Bargaining demands, 1956; 546698 (Box 14, Folder 4)
  - Bargaining reports, 1956-1958; 546697 (Box 14, Folder 5)
  - Bargaining demands, 1957; 546696 (Box 14, Folder 6)
  - International Bargaining for 1957 Contract, 1957-1958; 546695 (Box 14, Folder 7)
  - Bargaining demands and reports, 1959; 546694 (Box 14, Folder 8)
  - Bargaining demands and reports, 1960-1961; 546693 (Box 14, Folder 9)
  - Bargaining reports, 1962-1963; 546692 (Box 14, Folder 10)
  - Bargaining demands and proposed contract, 1963; 546691 (Box 14, Folder 11)
  - Correspondence: Bargaining and contract ratification, 1963; 546690 (Box 14, Folder 12)
  - American Arbitration Assn. referendum on contract ratification, 1963; 546689 (Box 14, Folder 13)
  - Bargaining Report, 1965; 546688 (Box 14, Folder 14)
  - Bargaining Reports, 1966; 546687 (Box 14, Folder 15)
  - CWA correspondence with Local 1150; management bargaining reports, 1967-1968, 1971; 546686 (Box 14, Folder 16)
  - Bargaining reports and correspondence, 1969-1972; 546685 (Box 14, Folder 17)
  - Bargaining demands, reports, 1971; 546684 (Box 14, Folder 18)
  - Bargaining demands and correspondence, 1972-1974; 546683 (Box 14, Folder 19)
  - Bargaining reports and correspondence, 1975-1978; 546682 (Box 14, Folder 20)
  - Bargaining demands, reports, 1979-1980; 546681 (Box 14, Folder 21)
  - Bargaining Demands, 1980; 546680 (Box 14, Folder 22)
  - Bargaining Demands, 1980, 1983; 546679 (Box 14, Folder 23)
  - Bargaining, 1980, 1983; 546678 (Box 14, Folder 24)
  - Bargaining, 1985-1989; 546677 (Box 14, Folder 25)
  - Bargaining I, 1983; 546676 (Box 15, Folder 1)
  - Bargaining II, 1983; 546675 (Box 15, Folder 2)
  - Contracts and Agreements: Union Proposal and Correspondence, 1970; 546674 (Box 15, Folder 3)
  - Contracts, 1977; 546673 (Box 15, Folder 4)
  - Memo of Agreement, 1958; 546672 (Box 15, Folder 5)
  - Memo of Agreement, 1959; 546671 (Box 15, Folder 6)
  - Memo of Agreement, 1960; 546670 (Box 15, Folder 7)
  - Memo of Agreement, 1963; 546669 (Box 15, Folder 8)
  - Memo of Agreement, 1967; 546668 (Box 15, Folder 9)
  - Memo of Agreement and correspondence, 1968; 546667 (Box 15, Folder 10)
  - Memo of Agreement, 1971; 546666 (Box 15, Folder 11)
  - Memo of Agreement, 1974; 546665 (Box 15, Folder 12)
  - Memo of Agreement, 1980; 546664 (Box 15, Folder 13)
  - Memo of Agreement, 1983; 546663 (Box 15, Folder 14)
  - Wage Schedules, 1954; 546662 (Box 15, Folder 15)
  - Wage Reopener, 1961; 546661 (Box 15, Folder 16)
  - Wage Reopener, 1962; 546660 (Box 15, Folder 17)
  - Wage Reopener, 1964-1966; 546659 (Box 15, Folder 18)
  - Arbitration Awards, 1967-1982; 546658 (Box 16, Folder 1)
  - Arbitration Awards: Local 1101, 1969-1974; 546657 (Box 16, Folder 2)
  - Arbitration Awards: Locals 1102, 1103, 1104, 1972-1981; 546656 (Box 16, Folder 3)
  - Arbitration Awards: Local 1106, 1972-1976; 546655 (Box 16, Folder 4)
  - Arbitration Awards: Locals 1107, 1108, 1109, 1120, 1122, 1126, 2205, 1969-1980; 546654 (Box 16, Folder 5)
  - Arbitration Awards: Local 1150, 1981; 546653 (Box 16, Folder 5a)
  - Arbitration Awards: Locals 1170, 1180, 1974-1981; 546652 (Box 16, Folder 6)
  - Misc. agreements with AT&T, 1952-1978; 546651 (Box 16, Folder 7)
  - Company policies and agreements: Division Level (Traffic Chairman's File), 1952-1961; 546650 (Box 16, Folder 8)
  - Arbitration cases, 1966-1968, 1971-1972; 546649 (Box 16, Folder 9)
  - Arbitration case (re: drug use) pp. 1-187, 1974-1975; 546648 (Box 16, Folder 10)
  - Arbitration case (re: drug use) pp. 188-349, 1974-1975; 546647 (Box 16, Folder 11)
  - Arbitration case (re: drug use) pp. 350-end, 1974-1975; 546646 (Box 16, Folder 12)
  - Arbitration Cases, 1975-1977; 546645 (Box 16, Folder 13)
  - Arbitration case (re: human rights law) I, 1977; 546644 (Box 16, Folder 13a)
  - Arbitration case (re: human rights law) II, 1977; 546643 (Box 16, Folder 13b)
  - Arbitration Cases, 1978-1983; 546642 (Box 16, Folder 14)
  - Arbitration Award Summaries, 1979-1984; 546641 (Box 16, Folder 14a)
- Series VII: Strikes and Work Stoppages, 1944-1983; 546617
  - Ohio Federation, 1944; 546639 (Box 17, Folder 1)
  - Illinois Telephone Traffic Union Strike; ACEW Strike; Kearney Case, 1945-1947; 546638 (Box 17, Folder 1a)
  - New York City Strike Report, 1947; 546637 (Box 17, Folder 2)
  - Work Assignments, 1950; 546636 (Box 17, Folder 3)
  - Strike Welfare Fund, 1952-1954; 546635 (Box 17, Folder 4)
  - General Telephone of CA Strike; White Plains Traffic Section Strike, 1963; 546634 (Box 17, Folder 5)
  - New York Telephone Company Lockout, 1964; 546633 (Box 17, Folder 6)
  - New York Plant Strike Settlement, 1967; 546632 (Box 17, Folder 7)
  - White Plains Traffic Section Strike, 1968; 546631 (Box 17, Folder 8)
  - Bell System Strike, 1968; 546630 (Box 17, Folder 9)
  - New York Telephone Company Lockout, 1969; 546629 (Box 17, Folder 10)
  - Western Electric Strike, 1970; 546628 (Box 17, Folder 11)
  - New York Plant Strike, 1971-1972; 546627 (Box 17, Folder 12)
  - O'Neil-Campbell affair, 1973-1974; 546626 (Box 17, Folder 13)
  - Strike Vote, 1974; 546625 (Box 17, Folder 14)
  - District 1 Strike Bulletins, 1975; 546624 (Box 17, Folder 15)
  - Easter Traffic problem, 1977; 546623 (Box 17, Folder 16)
  - AT&T Long Lines Work Stoppage, 1978; 546622 (Box 17, Folder 17)
  - Legal/Liability, 1979-1983; 546621 (Box 17, Folder 18)
  - Strike Benefits, 1980-1983; 546620 (Box 17, Folder 19)
  - Strike Bulletins, 1983; 546619 (Box 17, Folder 20)
  - Strike Preparation, 1989; 546618 (Box 17, Folder 21)
- Series VIII: Convention and Conference Records, 1944-1988; 546557
  - NFTW, 10th National Convention, 1944; 546616 (Box 17, Folder 22)
  - FLLTW, 1st Annual Convention, 1945; 546615 (Box 17, Folder 23)
  - AUTW-CIO Convention: report by VP C. Allen, 1948; 546614 (Box 17, Folder 24)
  - AUTW, TWOC-CIO, Presidents' Conference: report, 1948; 546613 (Box 17, Folder 25)
  - CWA, Founding Convention, proceedings, 1946; 546612 (Box 17, Folder 26)
  - CWA National Conventions, 1950, 1952-1954; 546611 (Box 17, Folder 27)
  - CWA National Conventions, 1952-1955; 546610 (Box 17, Folder 28)
  - CWA National Conventions, 1955; 546609 (Box 17, Folder 29)
  - CWA National Conventions, 1956; 546608 (Box 17, Folder 30)
  - CWA National Conventions, 1957-1958; 546607 (Box 17, Folder 31)
  - CWA National Conventions, 1959-1960; 546606 (Box 17, Folder 32)
  - CWA National Conventions, 1961-1963; 546605 (Box 17, Folder 33)
  - CWA National Conventions, 1964-1967; 546604 (Box 18, Folder 1)
  - CWA National Conventions, 1968-1969; 546603 (Box 18, Folder 2)
  - CWA National Conventions, 1970, 1972; 546602 (Box 18, Folder 3)
  - CWA National Conventions, 1973-1978; 546601 (Box 18, Folder 4)
  - CWA National Conventions, 1979; 546600 (Box 18, Folder 5)
  - CWA National Conventions, 1980; 546599 (Box 18, Folder 6)
  - CWA National Conventions, 1981-1982; 546598 (Box 18, Folder 7)
  - CWA National Conventions, 1983; 546597 (Box 18, Folder 8)
  - CWA National Conventions, 1984; 546596 (Box 18, Folder 9)
  - CWA National Community Services Conference, 1980-1981; 546595 (Box 18, Folder 10)
  - CWA National Conference on Minority Concerns, 1982; 546594 (Box 18, Folder 11)